Finding Aid for the Eiko Ishioka papers LSC.2288
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 12: Career, 1960-2011
  This series also contains material—mostly photographs and other images—that is unidentified and most likely relates to specific design projects or advertising campaigns.
  - Subseries 12.1: Photographs of Ishioka, 1965-2006
    Photographs, contact sheets, and slides of Ishioka publicity images, especially by photographer Brigitte Lacombe. Robert Mapplethorpe's portrait of Ishioka is also present. See Series 13 for personal snapshots of Ishioka.
    - Photographic portraits (publicity images), circa 1965-2006 (Box 198, Folder 2-6)
      Bulk is by photographer Brigitte Lacombe. Includes photographs, contact sheets, copies.
    - Photographic portraits: by Robert Mapplethorpe, 1983 (Box 737)
      Two portraits of Eiko Ishioka by Robert Mapplethorpe, one of which is color, framed and matted and the other, black and white and matted.
    - Photographs and contact sheets, circa 1970-1990, undated (Box 203, Folder 4-7, Box 207, Folder 10-12, Box 716, Folder 19-23)
      Photographs (mostly snapshots) and contact sheets of Ishioka with various people; some groups of contact sheets have images that appear to be personal. Contact sheets of Ishioka with Philip Glass are in box 203, folder 7.
    - Slides, 1970s (Box 501)
  - Subseries 12.2: Portfolios, 1962-2002
    Portfolios are mostly binders of slides, transparencies, and photographs of images of Ishioka's overall career work including posters, exhibitions, packaging, record covers, book and journal design, stage and film projects, and advertising. Some items may be related to production work for Eiko by Eiko or other books (transparencies), or to lectures given by Ishioka (slides). Some binders also have images of Ishioka with various colleagues.
    - Slides, transparencies, contact sheets, negatives, 1962-2002, undated (Box 198, Folder 7-9, Box 483, Box 484, Box 485, Box 486, Box 487, Box 488, Folder 1-6, Box 492)
      Images in box 485, fols 1-3 include Miles Davis, Leni Riefenstahl, Susan Sontag, Philip Glass, Faye Dunaway, Francis Ford Coppola. Binder in box 492 has images of Ishioka with Miles Davis, Francis Ford Coppola, and George Lucas.
    - Slides and transparencies: posters, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 493, Box 494)
      Posters include Apocalypse Now (box 493), Power Now, Hair, Tradition et Nouvelles Techniques, Hiroshima Appeals, L'Innocente, Koyaanisqatsi, New Music Media 2, Trois Couleurs (Bleu), Erco, Close Up of Japan, Crystal Silence, Holiday, various events. Includes images of final product and images used in posters.
    - Mounted images, undated (Box 705)
    - Graphic design transparencies: file box, circa 1970s (Box 714)
    - Binder labels, undated (Box 204, Folder 17)
  - Subseries 12.3: Writings, 1976-2005
    Published or drafts of writings by Ishioka for various publications, including her 1979 More magazine article about Leni Riefenstahl. See box 520 folder 2 for Ishioka's interview with Francis Ford Coppola. Concert programs are for Manhattan Transfer and Kimiko Kasai.
    - "Leni Riefenstahl: The Eternal Woman" (More magazine article), 1979 (Box 172, Folder 6, Box 515, Folder 2)
      Original magazines in box 515; copies of published article in box 172.
    - Matisse essay (copy), undated (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - "Cherry Blossoms through Banana Eyes" (copy), undated (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Various publications, 1976-1991 (Box 519, Folder 3-4, Box 520, Folder 1-2, Box 700, Folder 2)
    - Drafts (I Design?), circa 2005 (Box 701, Folder 6)
    - Drafts (also has some copies of published pieces), undated (Box 701, Folder 7, Box 702, Folder 1-5, Box 703)
    - Liner notes for concert programs, 1983, undated (Box 700, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 12.4: Correspondence, 1977-2009 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    Letters, postcards (bulk in Japanese).
  - Subseries 12.5: Unidentified projects or advertising, circa 1970-1979, undated
    Primarily photographs, contact sheets, transparencies, slides, and negatives relating to unidentified projects or advertising campaigns from the 1970s. Also includes some drawings and material that was most likely used for research purposes. Some items (especially in boxes 205-206) may relate to art direction work for Wild Times or other publications (see Series 7).
    Also contains items with identification but undetermined nature.
    - "Jiro Kimuri Jiro, TV screen shooting, experiment of water skimming:" transparencies, 1970s (Box 497)
    - "Hungary coverage:" slide binder, 1986 (Box 497)
    - Research or unidentified project: slides, 1970s (Box 501)
    - Unidentified projects or advertising (Box 169, Folder 10-11, Box 203, Folder 8-16, Box 205, Box 206, Box 207, Folder 6, Box 349, Folder 4, Box 429, Box 459, Folder 5, Box 488, Folder 7-8, Box 502, Box 503, Box 504, Box 505, Box 506, Box 507, Box 596, Box 712)
    - Various/unidentified poster production material (Box 59, Box 287, Box 169, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 12.6: Events, 1977-2009
    Material, mostly photographs and slides, relating to various conferences, lectures, and professional receptions.
    - Japan in Aspen conference: photographs and ephemera, 1979 (Box 198, Folder 10, Box 199, Folder 1-2, Box 716, Folder 1)
    - Design Conference in Aspen: photographs and ephemera, 1988 (Box 199, Folder 3-4)
    - Morisawa Awards International Typeface Competition: program, 1984 (Box 520, Folder 4)
    - International Typeface Contest reception: photograph, 1984 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - I Design party: photographs, circa 2005 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Adobe Photoshop workshop: slides, 1990 (Box 492)
    - Windows Cultural Forum: slides, 1990 (Box 492)
    - Lecture, UCLA Regents: poster (Box 36)
    - Lecture, Japan: poster (College of Art, Faculty of Advanced Art), 2005 (Box 6)
    - Unidentified events: photographs, 1977-2009, undated (Box 169, Folder 6, Box 200, Folder 1-6, Box 716, Folder 2-18)
      Bulk is snapshots; some (especially box 716 folders 10-18) may be personal photographs.
    - Unidentified events with Issey Miyake and others: photographs, 1980-1990, undated (Box 715, Folder 11-13)
    - Various events: slides, 1970s, 1985-1987, undated (Box 498, Box 501)
  - Subseries 12.7: Publicity, 1960-2011
    Publications containing articles about or interviews with Ishioka pertaining to her career generally. Publicity photographs are in Subseries 12.1.
    - Clippings, 1988-2007; some are copies (Box 169, Folder 7-8, Box 200, Folder 7, Box 704)
    - Publications: Super Art GoCoo, 1977-1981 (Box 509, Box 510)
    - Publications: Graphis, 1995, 2000-2004 (Box 511, Box 512)
    - Publications: Asahi Camera, 1976-1979 (Box 514)
    - Publications: More, 1978-1986 (Box 515)
      Bulk Parco-related.
    - Publications: various, 1960-2011, undated (Box 343, Folder 5, Box 520, Folder 5-7, Box 521, Box 522, Box 523, Box 524, Box 525, Box 526, Box 527, Box 528, Box 529, Box 530, Box 531, Box 532, Box 533, Box 534, Box 535, Box 536, Box 537, Box 538, Box 700, Folder 5-6)
      520-535: 1/2 doc boxes: 520: 1960-1972 521: 1973-1978 522: 1979-1982 523: 1983-1984 524: 1984-1985 525: 1985-1986 526: 1986-1991 527: 1992-1993 528: 1994-1998 529: 1999-2001 530: 2001-2002 531: 2002-2003 532: 2003-2005 533: 2005-2006 534: 2008-2011, undated 535: undated 536-538: bulk 1980s (mag boxes)
    - Poster prints (sports/desserts) with EI bio on reverse, undated (Box 597)
    - Ephemera, 1984, undated (Box 518, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 12.8: Awards, 1964-2008
    Numerous awards from Art Directors Club of Tokyo, ACE, ADC, Japan Packaging Competition (JPC), Japan Package Design Award (JPDA),Japan Advertising Artists Club (JAAC); awards are plaques, sculptural, and on paper, with some gifts included. ADC, Mitsio Katsui designed arts, Nippon Sendan Sho, and Yamana Sho award also included.
    - Shiju Hosho: event/party photographs, 2002 (Box 199, Folder 7-8)
    - Awards, 1964-2008 (Box 334, Box 335, Box 336, Box 337)
      Oversize awards held onsite at YRL.
  - Subseries 12.9: Art supplies, undated (Box 331, Box 332, Box 333)
    Pens, markers, pencils, crayons, ink, utensils, and Barbie dolls.
  - Subseries 12.10: Notes and ephemera, 1980s-2011
    - Notebooks, undated (Box 702, Folder 5)
      One notebook is "Video List," the other contains one page of notes.
    - Notes and ephemera, circa 1980s, 1992-2011, undated (Box 200, Folder 9, Box 702, Folder 6, Box 703)
    - Various projects: flyers, 1988-1991 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Peter Hammer Verlag calendar, 1998 (Box 187, Folder 7)
- Series 13: Personal, 1968-2011
  Primarily photographs and snapshots that do not appear to be work-related. Also present is a journal. See Series 11 for related audiovisual material.
  - Subseries 13.1: Photographs, 1968-1997, undated
    Includes snapshots and photo albums that appear to be mostly of a personal nature especially travels; New York City and Ishioka's apartment there; and events with family, friends, and colleagues such as parties, dinners, and weddings. Some photographs depict subjects that may overlap with professional endeavors.
    - New York City, 1971-1989, undated (Box 200, Folder 10-11, Box 717)
    - Japan, 1990, undated (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - Italy (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - France, undated (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Berlin, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - London, 1989 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Germany (Wagner home), 1997 (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Guam, circa 1977 (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Bali (?), 1994 (Box 201, Folder 6-9)
    - Hawaii (?), 1990 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Various locations (some unidentified), 1968-1993, undated (Box 202, Folder 2-4, Box 717, Folder 1-9)
      Snapshots of Doris Lessing in box 202, folder 4.
    - Various events, 1971-1990, undated (Box 202, Folder 5-8, Box 717, Folder 12-24)
      Events include with family members. Kimiko Kasai wedding photos are in box 717, folder 23.
    - Coppola family, 1987-1992, undated (Box 203, Folder 1, Box 716, Folder 25)
      Various events as well as travel to Belize; includes some contact sheets.
    - Ishioka and others, circa 1970-1988, undated (Box 203, Folder 2-3, Box 716, Folder 24-26)
      Bulk of items in box 716 is loose snapshots of Ishioka with family and friends, not attached to larger rolls.
    - Snapshots of others, 1968-1986, undated (Box 716, Folder 27)
    - Cats, 1980-1989, undated (Box 716, Folder 28)
    - Various objects, 1971-1989, undated (Box 716, Folder 29)
    - Negatives and transparencies, 1988-1989, undated (Box 421, Folder 8-9, Box 488, Folder 9)
    - Slides, 1970s-1982 (Box 500, Box 501)
      Includes travels and various locations especially New York City, San Francisco, Hawaii, Europe, and Bulgaria (perhaps on location for "Autumn in Sofia," see Series 7 Subseries 7.2)
    - Loose ephemera, undated (Box 716, Folder 30)
      Ephemera found in storage box with loose snapshots (now in boxes 715-717).
  - Subseries 13.2: Journal, 2009-2011 (Box 701, Folder 1-5)
    Handwritten on loose notebook paper.
    Journal is foldered as is in reverse chronological order.
- Series 14: Works by others, 1960s-1990s
  Mostly posters in Ishioka's collection that were not designed by her, for various exhibitions, events, and films, as well as fashion posters (especially Issey Miyake), and advertising. Also present is artwork by Peter Beard and several other artists.
  - Subseries 14.1: Posters, 1960s-1990s
    Contains various posters not designed by Ishioka. Posters are for exhibitions, events, performing arts, fashion, and advertising.
    Festivals and events include other posters for Hiroshima Appeals, Tradition et Nouvelles Techniques, and Expo '70. Music includes other posters for New Music Media 1 and 2; also Talking Heads Stop Making Sense and several Beatles posters. The bulk of fashion posters are for Issey Miyake. Box 89 has a poster signed by Christo to EI.
    Boxes 285-320 (oversize posters) are held at YRL.
    - Art and graphic art exhibitions (Box 87, Box 88, Box 89, Box 90, Box 286)
    - Festivals and events (Box 91, Box 92)
    - Film (Box 93)
    - Music (Box 94, Box 95, Box 285)
    - Stage productions (Box 96)
    - Fashion (Box 97, Box 98)
    - Advertising: Parco (Box 99)
    - Other (Box 100, Box 185, Folder 10, Box 101)
    - Unidentified Chinese posters (Box 285)
    - INTERNAL Preservation copies [of some] (Box 102)
  - Subseries 14.2: Artwork, 1973-1992
    - Peter Beard, 1973-1977, undated (Box 185, Folder 2, Box 212)
    - Joel-Peter Witkin: "Lisa Lyon as Hercules" (photograph), 1983 (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - Anita Siegel, 1977 (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Sue Coe, undated (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - "Kevin's DNA", undated (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Hans Bellmer "Portrait d'unica avec l'oeil-sexe", circa 1962 (Box 756)
    - Various and unidentified, 1973-1992, undated (Box 172, Folder 4-5, Box 185, Folder 5-6, Box 204, Folder 16, Box 212)
      Includes works on paper, collage, and prints.
- Series 15: Books from the library of Eiko Ishioka
  Contains books about and/or designed by Ishioka (career) as well as her library of books on various topics. Career books include Eiko by Eiko, Eiko on Stage, and books designed for Kadokawa, Parco, and others.
  Books in this collection will be individually cataloged under the SPAC code EIKO.
  - Career (Box 539, Box 544, Box 545, Box 546, Box 547, Box 548, Box 628)
  - Career (Box 540, Box 541, Box 542, Box 543, Box 667, Box 668, Box 669, Box 670, Box 671, Box 672, Box 673, Box 674, Box 675, Box 676, Box 678, Box 679, Box 680, Box 681, Box 682, Box 683, Box 684, Box 685, Box 686, Box 687, Box 688, Box 689, Box 706)
    Includes Leni Riefenstahl exhibition books Nuba and Life, Tamara de Lempicka: The Myth of the Portrait, Spectral Women, Parco View (box 543). Kadokawa paperbacks are in boxes 668-669. Textbooks are in box 673.
  - Career (Box 667, Box 718)
  - Art (Box 561, Box 562, Box 564, Box 565, Box 566, Box 567, Box 568, Box 569, Box 570, Box 571, Box 572, Box 573, Box 574, Box 575, Box 576, Box 577, Box 578, Box 579, Box 580, Box 581, Box 582, Box 583, Box 584, Box 585, Box 586, Box 587, Box 588, Box 615)
  - Art (Box 641, Box 642, Box 643, Box 644, Box 645, Box 646, Box 647, Box 648, Box 649, Box 650, Box 651, Box 652)
  - Photography (Box 549, Box 550, Box 551, Box 552, Box 553, Box 554, Box 555, Box 556, Box 557, Box 558, Box 559, Box 560, Box 561, Box 562, Box 563, Box 612)
  - Photography (Box 651, Box 652, Box 653, Box 654, Box 655, Box 656, Box 657, Box 658, Box 665)
  - Graphic and interior design (Box 589, Box 590, Box 591, Box 592, Box 593, Box 594, Box 595, Box 600, Box 601, Box 602, Box 630)
  - Graphic and interior design (Box 659, Box 660, Box 661, Box 662, Box 663, Box 664, Box 665)
  - Fashion (Box 601, Box 602, Box 603, Box 604, Box 605, Box 606, Box 607, Box 608, Box 609, Box 610, Box 611, Box 612, Box 615, Box 616)
  - Fashion (Box 646, Box 647, Box 648, Box 649, Box 650, Box 736)
  - Architecture (Box 611, Box 612, Box 613, Box 614, Box 615, Box 618)
  - Architecture (Box 666)
  - Film (Box 620, Box 622, Box 623, Box 629)
  - Film (Box 677)
  - Theater (Box 620, Box 624, Box 628)
  - Other (Box 563, Box 615, Box 616, Box 617, Box 618, Box 619, Box 620, Box 621, Box 623, Box 625, Box 626, Box 627, Box 628, Box 629, Box 630, Box 631)
    Categories include literature, music, science, nature, travel, dance, food, culture, biography, history, graphic novels, children's literature.
  - Other (Box 639, Box 640, Box 664, Box 666, Box 677)
    Includes biography, culture, food, music.
  - Other languages (Box 632, Box 633, Box 634, Box 635, Box 636, Box 637, Box 638, Box 639)
  - Oversize
    Includes Eiko by Eiko and Eiko on Stage.
    Shelved individually.
  - Duplicate books: Career (Box 721, Box 722, Box 723, Box 724, Box 725, Box 726, Box 735)
    Duplicates are not cataloged. Box 721 includes Eiko by Eiko (English, Japanese, and French) and Eiko on Stage; box 722 includes Leni: Life, Tamara de Lempicka, Parco Views; box 723 includes Nuba.
  - Duplicate books: career/ Kadokowa (Box 727, Box 728, Box 729, Box 730)
    Duplicates are uncataloged. Most of these appear to be Kadokawa publications; paperbacks are in box 730.
- Series 16: Preservation posters
  - 10th International Biennial Exhibition of Prints in Tokyo (Box 61)
  - Akira Kirosawa whole picture (Box 61)
  - Aid & Comfort II (Box 61)
  - AMPO--1970--EXPO (Box 61, Box 62)
  - Apocolypse Now (Brando), 2 copies (Box 294)
  - Apocolypse Now (Helicopters), 4 copies - 1 signed (Box 293)
  - Bagunca (Box 62)
  - Bibari (Box 62)
  - Bram Stoker's Dracula: [title: red with black lettering (vertical)], [red robe], [couple Medusa/Werewolf (vertical)] (Box 64)
  - Bram Stoker's Dracula: eyes [horiz], 2 copies (Box 299)
  - Bram Stoker's Dracula: titles - 2 full, 1 "Dr", 1 "acula" [horiz] (Box 301)
  - Bram Stoker's Dracula: Medusa/Werewolf - 2 full; 2 of each triptych [horiz] (Box 300)
  - The Cell (Box 62)
  - Chushingura Opera (Box 62)
  - Close Up of Japan (two copies, one signed) (Box 62)
  - Crystal Silence series (Box 63)
  - Diana: Hot Hot Sandal; She Experienced Wearing High Heels; You, Wear Pink Sandals; Sandal Won in Brown Summer; Sandal Invited. Summer Got Burnt; "Wait Until I Take My Boots Off;" Shoes Occasionally Make a Woman Bold; Mike! Don't Touch the Shoes! (Box 63)
  - Don't Stare at the Poster; Be a Poster (Box 64)
  - Eiko by EIko: poster and cover proof (Box 64)
  - Eiko on Stage: cover proof (Box 64)
  - Elvis. (Box 64)
  - Epoca (Box 65)
  - Erco (Box 66)
  - Expo '70 (Box 65)
  - Form and Flower (from Tokyo: Form & Spirit) (Box 65)
  - George Szell Cleveland Orchestra (Box 65)
  - Give Blood Save Life (Box 65)
  - Gom (Box 65)
  - Habitat (Box 65)
  - Hair (Box 67)
  - Hiroshima Appeals (Box 67)
  - Holiday (both versions) (Box 67)
  - The Human Century (Box 67)
  - ID for Man (Box 67)
  - Ingot (Box 67)
  - International Canvas Furniture Design Competition (Box 67)
  - Issey Miyake and Issey Miyake Show (Box 68)
  - Japan Shop (Box 68)
  - Kadokawa Books - Hey, Hot Man! This Is a Hot Book! Hi, Hit Woman! This Is a Hit Book! (1 of 2 parts); Alone. Read Today. Open Tomorrow.; Having Trips Just For Reading Books; Don't Want To Be A Boring Adult (version one: rain, cars); Alone. Read Light. Open Wind.; Don't Want To Be A Boring Adult (version two: sitting on porch, reg and smaller); Page Rang. A Woman was in the Wind; Book Girls Have Already Become A Negative Symbol; Want to Hold. This Day. This Book. (Box 68)
  - Kadokawa Books: Having Books To Read Til They Get Worn Out.;The Book That Turns into Sand; The Book That Travels; smaller posters (Box 69)
  - Kadokawa Books: San Francisco Book Fair HORIZ (Box 313)
  - Kissa Sport (Box 69)
  - Kissa (Box 70)
  - Koyaanisqatsi, 2 copies (Box 294)
  - Leni Riefenstahl: Film/Life (Box 70, Box 71)
  - Leni Riefenstahl: Nuba (Box 71)
  - Life (Box 72)
  - L'Inhumaine (Box 72)
  - L'Innocente, 2 = 1 of each (Box 294)
  - Maboroshi no Onna (Box 72)
  - Marlene (Box 72)
  - Mio. (Box 72)
  - Mitsuko Uchida piano recital (Box 72)
  - Morisawa Award International Typeface Competition '84 (Box 72)
  - The Morning Schedule (Box 72)
  - New Music Media (Box 72)
  - New Music Media 2 in Tsumagoi (Box 72)
  - Parco: This Is the Poster for Parco - Faye Dunaway, 307: horiz - 1 copy (Box 73, Box 307)
  - Parco: Can West Wear East? (5 regular size w/ 4 signed; 1 smaller), 307: horiz - 2 copies (Box 73, Box 307)
  - Parco: Faye Dunaway horiz (Box 307)
  - Parco: All That Jyoji! horiz, 2 eng 1 Japanese 1 other version (Box 305)
  - Parco: Issey Miyake and Twelve Black Women; The Nightingale Sings for No One but Herself series; Fly with Issey Miyake (Box 74)
  - Parco: Kimiko; There Are No Rails on the High Heel Express; Salome; Don't Stare at the Nude; Be Naked; A Woman Can Feel a Foreign Country (2 versions); Dressed to Kill and No Place to Go (Box 75)
  - Parco: Ah, Our Roots!; My Dear Superstar; My Dear Superwoman; You Are Fantastic! How Old Are You?; Anti-Sentimentalism (version 1); Life Is Short, The Night Is Longer; Girls Be Ambitious! (Box 76)
  - Parco: Parco Part 2; Tamara de Lempicka; Summer in Parco; Men! Let's Become More Beautiful for Women! (version 1) (Box 77)
  - Parco: Kenji Sawada: Who Will Make the Pulse of Our Time Beat Faster?; The Day Has Come to Speak about Men; Who Will Ring the Heart of this Era. (Box 77)
  - Parco: The Kimono. Very Parco.; The Book. Very Parco.; The Dress. Very Parco.; The Restaurant. Very Parco.; The Shoes. Very Parco.; The Music. Very Parco.; The Sports. Very Parco.; The Theater. Very Parco. (Box 78)
  - Parco: Dominique Sanda; Be Natural. Go Nature.; 12.12.Open; Shinsaibashi Opening December 12th! Men, Let's Be More Beautiful for Women.(version 2); Of People Who Are Sensitive to Live; Sense of PARCO.; Anti-Sentimentalism (version 2); Goodbye My Hometown, Fashion Has No Borders. (Box 79)
  - Parco: Shibuya Women are Burning with Tomorrow.; Parco's Goodbye to the Ocean; Our Summer; The Wind Of PARCO In The Eyes. December 1st The Birth of Chibaginza; Shibuya Men Are Gazing at Tomorrow.; Summer of PARCO's Color - Azule; Summer of PARCO's Color - Brown; Don't Stare at the Nude. Be Naked. (version 2); Sense of PARCO Is Inheritated, or Not.; smaller posters; Hamlet (Box 80)
  - Parco: Kenji Sawada (oversize, 2 ver); Dominique Sanda; I Have Come Thousands of Miles in Search of You, Vision of Spectral Wonders [HORIZ] (Box 306)
  - Pierre Cardin (Box 81)
  - Ring of the Nibelung (Box 81)
  - Sanyo: Sanyoing is Fashioning Sanyo: I Am Very Woman Sanyo: I Am Very Woman [Annie Leibovitz] Sanyo: Fiat Sanyo: Coat (Box 82)
  - Sanyo: Sanyoing is Fashioning, Fiat, I Am Very Woman (2 versions), Coat (4 versions) HORIZ (Box 312, Box 313)
  - Seibu (Box 83)
  - Shiki Fabric House France (Box 83)
  - Shiseido: Sun Oil Shiseido: Sunscreen Shiseido: Beauty Cake Shiseido: Honey Cake (Box 83)
  - Shiseido: Summer '62; Summer; [woman head, couple on beach] (Box 84)
  - Shop System Show (Box 84)
  - Summer Grand Concert Saburo Kitajima (Box 84)
  - Tokyo Animation Festival '66 (Box 84)
  - Tokyu; [logo], [subway poster], [two elderly women], [child], [five girls], [elderly man], [couple with birds], [man with child] (Box 85)
  - Tradition et Nouvelles Techniques (Box 86)
  - Trois Couleurs: Bleu (Box 86)
  - UCLA Regents lecture EI (Box 86)
  - Wild Times magazine cover [alien sitting on bench] (Box 86)
  - YES NO NO YES (Box 86)
  - Poster duplicates: Parco (Can West Wear East?), Dracula (vertical: wolf and medusa) (Box 597)